let questionsSet = [
  {
    question: "How was Sri Lanka formerly known?",
    option1: "Burma",
    option2: "Ceylon",
    option3: "Formosa",
    option4: "Nyasaland",
    rightAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which strait separates Sri Lanka from India?",
    option1: "Palk Strait",
    option2: "Davis Strait",
    option3: "Cook Strait",
    option4: "Johore Strait",
    rightAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the capital of Sri Lanka?",
    option1: "Colombo",
    option2: "Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte",
    option3: "Galle",
    option4: "Kandy",
    rightAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the longest river in Sri Lanka?",
    option1: "Nilwala",
    option2: "Amban",
    option3: "Mahaweli",
    option4: "Kalu",
    rightAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the highest point in Sri Lanka?",
    option1: "Pidurutalagala",
    option2: "Adam's Peak",
    option3: "Kirigalpotta",
    option4: "Haritha Montain",
    rightAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the largest national park in Sri Lanka?",
    option1: "Yala National Park",
    option2: "Minneriya National Park",
    option3: "Horton Plains National Park",
    option4: "Wilpattu National Park",
    rightAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which is the largest city in Sri Lanka by population?",
    option1: "Colombo",
    option2: "Kandy",
    option3: "Galle",
    option4: "Jaffna",
    rightAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the largest lake in Sri Lanka?",
    option1: "Gregory Lake",
    option2: "Beira Lake",
    option3: "Bolgoda Lake",
    option4: "Maduru Oya Reservoir",
    rightAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the famous beach destination in Sri Lanka known for its golden sandy shores and surfing opportunities?",
    option1: "Mirissa",
    option2: "Unawatuna",
    option3: "Bentota",
    option4: "Arugam Bay",
    rightAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the UNESCO World Heritage Site in Sri Lanka known for its ancient rock fortress?",
    option1: "Polonnaruwa",
    option2: "Adam's Peak",
    option3: "Sigiriya",
    option4: "Anuradhapura",
    rightAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
];
